Do you believe in parallel worlds?
If someone suddenly told you
he’s from a parallel world
would you believe him?
And he knew everything
from the room I live in
to what I eat for breakfast.
But I’ve never really
crossed paths with him before.
You've never met him,
or you just didn't notice?
You and me, being a couple?
If he doesn’t know
me here, I’ll start over.
I’m going to be your boyfriend.
Please let me make a move on you.
Ai Cir, what the hell are you doing?
Where’s Phukan?
What are you talking about?
I’ll go get the doctor.
Phu.
Phukan, my boyfriend.
Listen to me, Ai Cir.
You got hit by a car.
You’re confused right now.
I’ve known you my whole life,
and you don’t have a boyfriend.
You’ve never had one.
I’m asking where Phukan is!
I don’t know.
I’ll go get the doctor.
If you’re an ordinary person
who’s always lived an ordinary life...
I’m telling you, I know
exactly how that felt.
I was no different from anyone else
graduating from high school
and getting into college.
Waking up late, running late for class.
Cramming the night before exams.
Copying homework from friends.
Using AI to help with assignments.
Hey. Who's that?
Fighting with friends
and making up afterward.
And I thought I’d live that
simple life to the end of my days.
Until someone knocked
my door and told me...
he was from a parallel world.
EP II: The Identity of the Stranger
Please let me make a move on you.
Gosh, what should I do?
Forget it. Whatever will be, will be.
I know it sounds crazy
but I’m about to tell you the chaotic
story of my life from here on.
Phu.
Are you okay?
No.
I keep running into P’ Cir
wherever I go lately.
Ai Jin says I just didn’t notice
but I never ran into him before this.
Tee, think about it.
I mean, how could someone like me
have a chance to run into P’ Cir?
But it’s been like that
for the past few days now.
I’ve been wearing the lucky color
and hanging this doll
exactly as the books say.
But I don’t know why
everything is so chaotic.
I think he likes you.
No way. Impossible.
A guy like P’ Cir likes me?
Impossible.
That’s never going to happen.
Even if the world ends,
it’s still impossible.
How many times have you said no, Phu?
So how do you explain P’ Cir’s actions?
Everyone knows that
he's totally the type
who doesn’t care about anyone.
Super introverted.
A handsome who’s quiet,
withdrawn, with walls built around him.
Anyone trying to get through
would just hit those walls.
And what’s this?
He waited around just to give you stuff?
Trust me, P’ Cir likes you.
That’s not true.
Tee, look at Phu.
He doesn’t believe me.
So why do you think
there’s no way he’d like you?
Because I’m the least
interesting person in the group.
Huh?
You see, Ai Achi is the campus
prince and Jin is super cool.
You’re the campus belle and a cheerleader.
And you’re a total package.
If anyone’s gonna be liked,
it’s gotta be you guys.
Not me.
Phu, you seriously don’t
realize how cute you are?
It wouldn’t be surprising if he likes you.
But didn’t he get hit by a car?
His brain might’ve...
you know, been affected.
Hello.
It’s me.
Hey!
How did you get my number?
Because I’m your boyfriend.
Please don’t joke around.
I never joke around.
Are you scared?
Am I crossing the line?
I’m not scared. I’m just… surprised.
So why are you calling me?
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
Miss you.
That’s all I wanted to say.
Study hard, okay?
Is it P’ Cir?
What did he say?
Nalin, please tell me there’s
no such thing as parallel worlds.
Like Marvel, Dr. Strange,
Earth-66, or something like that.
They aren’t real, right?
What? What parallel worlds?
I know right? How could it be possible?
If they do exist, then this
P’ Cir isn’t the P’ Cir we know.
He's another P’ Cir, that’s
why he knows everything.
Even though I’m into
all this spiritual stuff
I still can’t bring myself to believe it.
And he said he missed me…
- Miss you?
- Really?
P’ Cir said he missed you?
Well… I... I need to pee.
I’ll go pee first.
Hey!
I wanna know what’s inside.
Sweets.
Knock, knock, knock. Who’s there?
Damn it, Ai Rome,
I’m soaked because of you!
The fuck? Are you a dog or something?
Why so serious?
You’re yelling at me like I got you soaked.
What? You think I can just magically
make the rain or storm happen?
You’re making no sense.
Damn, cursing at me like I’m the rain god.
Watch out, or lightning’s
gonna hit you right on the head.
More like your head!
How could it not be your fault?
I shouldn’t have gone
to buy fish food with you.
Damn, I thought it’d be a small bag
but it turned out to be this huge!
Wrong, you idiot. Only this big.
Oh.
Seriously, are you raising fish
to sell at the market or something?
Bastard.
It took forever to drop off the fish
food at your place and come back.
And now look! It’s pouring!
Don’t you dare look down on my babies.
My koi are worth hundreds
of thousands each!
- You’re not making any sense. I’m out.
- You’re one to talk.
Bastard.
You're talking crap.
Wait, Ai Cir, where are you going?
Class is about to start.
Is it raining hard outside?
Can’t you really tell?
And where are you going?
Phu always forgets his umbrella.
His class should be over now.
I’ll go give him the umbrella.
Hey wait! But the prof’s almost here!
You’re gonna skip class like this?
Come on, just let him go.
It’s his life, you know.
You’re being way too nosy.
It’s not like I want to
stick my nose in his life.
But think about it.
If he forgets to go to the hospital
today, who are they gonna call?
Sir Isaac Newton?
Isaac Newton my ass!
Of course they’re gonna call you.
Don’t ask a stupid question
when you already know.
Not now, please. Not now.
I don’t have a ride.
Mr. Angel, can I please have
an umbrella fall right in front of me?
I promise I’ll return it to
the exact spot when I’m done.
Ugh, I’m gonna end up
like a soaked puppy again.
Was I too late?
How did you get here?
You forgot an umbrella again.
Yes, I did. But how did you know?
I won’t ask anymore.
I’ve been asking that question
so much lately, it’s become a habit.
I’m not curious anymore.
So… why are you all soaked?
You have an umbrella.
I just found out it was
raining, so I rushed over.
Here, let me help.
Sorry, it’s a habit.
Do you always do this?
I mean, carry things for me
bring me an umbrella,
and keep helping me.
‘Phu.’
Yes?
Not ‘me’.
Can you refer to yourself as ‘Phu’?
No way.
Why are you laughing?
You’re still the same.
Are you saying…
I sound like Phukan from the other world?
You believe me now?
I don’t know.
If I don’t believe you,
then it means you’re crazy.
But since I don’t want you to be crazy
I’ll try to make myself believe you.
And what if I say yes?
What if I tell you that you don’t
want to refer to yourself as Phu
but in the end, you will?
I think we need to talk.
If I guess the passcode correctly...
will you refer to yourself as Phu?
Don't you think I could be scared of you?
Sorry, I got too ahead of myself.
So tell me, what passcode did I set?
Can I really answer that?
Of course. I’m asking, aren’t I?
You're as cute as ever,
always so kind to me.
P’ Cir.
The passcode.
It’s your dad’s birthday.
Now, can you finally tell…
Phu
whether you always carry things
for Phu like this in that world?
Phu.
Well, you guessed the code right,
so I’m just doing what I promised.
Please come in.
We have a lot to talk about.
P’ Cir!
Phu, I've missed you
so much, I’m going crazy.
Please let go of me.
You haven't changed at all.
You're still the person I know.
You care about everyone.
It may seem like... I'm out of my mind.
Anyone else would have yelled
at me by now, but you still care.
When I woke up, I thought
I was really going insane.
Phu.
Everyone told me that
we don’t know each other.
That you don’t know me.
You’ve been going on about dating
Nong Phukan since you woke up
but you’ve never even spoken to him!
I don’t want to scare you
but I don’t know what to do
to make you believe me.
P’ Cir, let go.
I’m sorry.
It’s… okay.
You’re just…
confusing me with another me.
You said we’re a couple.
When exactly did that happen?
In high school.
When I was in Grade 10?
Yes, during the sports day.
But we were on different teams.
You were on team yellow,
I was on team blue.
You were a drum major.
The third baton—I was forced into it.
You kept dropping the baton on your
head just so you could get replaced.
Your head would get a bump every day
because they wouldn’t let you switch.
How did you know?
We didn’t even know
each other back then.
Let me ask you something.
You and me…
The other me.
How did we get to know each other
when we never even talked to
or met each other in this world?
We’ve talked before.
I can ignore this call.
No, you should answer it.
I’m not going.
I told you I'm not going.
I’m hanging up.
Was that P’ Wim?
You know Ai Wim?
Well, if it’s P’ Wim,
who doesn’t know him?
He’s both the student
president and a university MC.
I see him all the time.
But you didn’t see me?
Are you upset?
P’ Cir.
P’ Cir krub.
- P’ Cir krub.
- I’m supposed to get my stitches out today.
Oh, then why aren’t you going?
I’d rather stay here.
With you.
No, you to get your stitches out.
What time is your appointment?
Don’t tell me it’s now?
Get up, you need to go now! Up!
I want to stay with you.
No, you need to get your stitches removed.
Get up. Don't act so heavy, get up!
Come on.
Are you the patient’s friend?
Why didn’t you bring
him back to the hospital?
The doctor already said to monitor
his condition for a few more days.
So how could he just run off like that?
Do you realize we were all over
the hospital searching for him?
Well… I…
You’re going to say he’s fine?
But Mr. Rames was unconscious for
three days without any known cause.
What would you do
if his condition worsened?
Even if the brain CT scan
shows nothing wrong
how could he just sneak out
of the hospital like that?
That’s just childish!
So when exactly was he
supposed to get discharged?
Today.
There’s still the concussion issue as well.
What?
It’s nothing serious.
Mr. Rames woke up and
was just a little confused
but his memory will settle down soon.
You don’t have to worry.
And please don’t let him run
away from the hospital again.
Though it’s better if he doesn’t
end up getting admitted again.
Confused? Concussion?
What if everything he's done…
My head hurts.
Phu, what’s wrong?
Are you not feeling well?
I’m fine.
Please don’t make me worry.
What are you doing?
But you said your head hurts.
It’s your fault.
Why did you run away from the hospital?
I wanted to see you.
But that's not a reason
to run away from the hospital.
Aren’t you going to talk to me?
P’ Cir krub.
Sneaky boy.
Can you answer me now?
I...
I wanted to make sure that this place…
this world, has you in it.
Everyone tells me you’re not my boyfriend.
They say…
I need to get plenty of rest,
and that I'm confused.
But I’m not confused.
See? You’re still here with me.
You do realize, don’t you?
This Phu right here isn’t that Phukan.
That’s true.
You’re not my boyfriend yet.
Even though I’m not,
I can still worry about you.
And if you want me to worry about you
you have to promise me that you
won’t run away from the hospital
skip your doctor’s appointments,
or cause trouble for anyone.
Do you understand?
What if I say no?
Please, P’ Cir.
Please.
Promise me you won’t do it again.
No more running away
from the hospital, okay?
Sneaky boy.
How did it end up like this?
Ai Phu, you shouldn’t
have made that promise.
You keep asking trouble for every day.
Thank you for taking me home.
But I should be the one
taking the patient home.
Not the other way around.
It's only right that I took you home.
Your car’s being repaired, right?
How did you—
I won’t ask anymore.
Take care on your way home.
Don’t worry about me.
I’m already home.
My room’s just downstairs.
In this building?
You’ve already promised me.
So, see you tomorrow.
You and I live in the same condo? For real?
Someone like him would actually like me?
He’s not from another planet, right?
Definitely an alien.
No doubt.
Did you wait long?
I just got here.
I don’t think so.
Look, the water’s already warm.
You just got out of the hospital.
What if you get sick again?
The nurse warned you
to take care of yourself.
But you'll get sunstroke
if you sit in the sun like this.
Don’t underestimate the weather here.
Be careful, or you'll die from heatstroke.
P' Cir, I’m being serious.
So am I.
Then why are you smiling?
You don’t make me feel like
you’re someone else at all.
I’m glad you’re letting us
get to know each other.
Like this.
Hey!
What’s wrong, Phu?
Shit, I left the clothes out.
I’m screwed.
Wait, Phu! Wait! Hold on!
I need to grab my uniform.
I don’t have any clean ones left.
I’ll do it.
It’s okay, I’ll do it.
I said I’ll do it. Come here.
P’ Cir!
Let me go, I’m not being stubborn.
I’ll do it. Just stay here.
Here.
Are you teasing me?
Worry about yourself first.
Sit down.
You’re one to talk.
Come here, I’ll dry your hair for you.
Seriously, you worry
about me but not yourself?
Because someone always
forgets to think about himself.
You're not scolding me, are you?
I wouldn’t dare scold you.
P’ Cir, I’m sorry! Does it hurt?
Let me take a look.
Does it hurt?
I'm sorry, I didn’t mean to.
Phu.
Stay still. Should we
have a doctor look at it?
Phu.
I'm sorry, I forgot you just had
your stitches removed. So sorry.
- I didn’t mean to.
- Phu!
Yes?
If you don't get off me,
don’t say I didn’t warn you.
Well...
I’d better change into something
else before I catch a cold.
Makes me think of the old times.
What’s this, P’ Cir?
Paper cup phone.
I know that.
You know, I used to help a kid
make these for homework.
and brought one to school to play with.
But my friends said I was acting too old.
Didn't you ask me how
we got to know each other?
Are you saying we got to
know each other through this?
Knock, knock… knock.
- Give it back!
- This way! This way!
Catch it!
It's dangerous. Give it back!
- Let us play with it for a bit.
- Throw it to me!
Now you've made me angry!
Ooh, you're angry?
- Come take it if you can!
- One more time.
Throw it to me.
Shit!
Shit, the Grade 12 room is downstairs.
Phu, it’s yours. Take it back.
Hey, you can't just ditch me like this.
Hey, what’s that?
Someone's tugging on the string.
Pull it back.
I can’t. Look, someone’s really tugging it.
Just throw it away.
No one will know it’s from our room.
- No one knows my ass!
- Do it.
Above us is the rooftop, so how
could they not know it’s from our room?
Then go ahead and talk.
We’re out of this. Go ahead.
Here I go.
Knock, knock, knock. Who’s there?
Nong Grade 10 calling
P’ Grade 12, is anyone there?
If you hear me, please
send an alien signal back.
Hey, someone’s answering!
- Go ahead, keep talking.
- Yeah.
Can I have the cup back?
If you want it back,
you have to guess who I am.
Wait a second!
That’s definitely not it.
You got the wrong story.
When did I ever smile sweetly?
Who put that filter on me?
You really answered me like that.
I clearly remember that when you walked in
you were shaking with
fear and kept saying sorry.
But you were too cute, I couldn’t
bring myself to scold you.
That was the first time we met.
That’s not true. No one answered me.
The you in this world didn’t answer me.
The me in this world must be stupid.
No, you’re not.
Phukan in this world might be too
slow to catch up with the cup thieves.
You believe me?
I was going to talk to you
about this, so might as well now.
Apart from knowing my passcode
what else can you show me
to prove we're a couple?
What do you want me to do?
What else do you know about me?
You believe in auspicious colors.
Everyone knows that.
So you bought a white car since
it's for Thursday-born people.
And your mom said
blue cars are hard to sell.
You might've heard it from someone.
You don’t wear lucky colors on your clothes
but you do in your underwear.
Everyone knows that too.
Today’s Saturday, so you’re wearing purple.
Probably with a guitar pattern.
How did you know?
It’s your favorite underwear.
- But I like it.
- Oh!
It looks cute on you.
One more thing.
There’s a mole on your right hip,
a palm below your waist.
Hey!
How did you know?
Believe me now?
What choice do I have?
I didn’t even know about the mole before.
So, you’ve taken off…
Phu.
Yes?
You might not know me in this world.
I'm not your boyfriend or your lover.
But… can I just stay close to you?
What a modest wish.
I know you want to pat my head.
Then I'll give you a bonus.
You can pat my head anytime you want.
Let me ask for this too.
Hope it’s not too modest.
Sawasdee krub, P’ Cir.
Where’s Phu?
Probably in the cafeteria.
You wanna see him?
No, I have class.
I think you should tell him the truth.
What does that mean?
What do you know?
Nothing much.
I'm just rambling.
It’s all up to you.
I’m just saying.
I’m off now.
Maybe he’s really from another world.
He knows things you didn’t even know about.
Fine, I’ll believe him.
But you’re not his boyfriend, Ai Phu.
I mean, you are, but
not the you in this world.
Listen, Ai Phu.
Phukan is P’ Cir’s boyfriend.
But that Phukan isn’t you.
Is that clear?
Yeah, crystal clear.
So what are you gonna do next?
I don’t know.
How can he be this ridiculously handsome?
And…
His lips are...
super soft too.
So crazy handsome.
With those lips and nose
put together on his sharp face...
who could keep their heart from racing?
No.
The Phukan P’ Cir wants
to see isn’t you, Ai Phu.
He’s your boyfriend in another world.
You shouldn’t bite off
more than you can chew.
Did I say I was gonna do something?
Yeah, you did.
You said a lot too.
You were voicing your thoughts
out loud and talking to yourself.
The whole cafeteria
thinks you’re crazy now.
- Ai Jin.
- What?
Take a seat.
What’s up, buddy?
I’ve made up my mind.
I’m gonna help P’ Cir return to that world.
I don’t think you should.
No, I’ve made up my mind.
The person who’s hurting isn’t just
this P’ Cir, but also the other me.
This P’ Cir says I’m his boyfriend.
Then what if the P’ Cir who’s never
talked to me go to that Phukan?
If your boyfriend suddenly changed
who do you think is the most
heartbroken right now?
I know my heart skips a beat for him
but I don’t want to come between lovers.
I’ve made up my mind.
I’m gonna go see P’ Cir.
Clear the plate for me.
This is so tangled up, Ai Phu.
Everyone’s just as much of a headache.
There’s gotta be a way.
There must be shamans or spiritual
masters who can send him back.
Or maybe we need to create
a magic circle like Doctor Strange?
Oh, but he came here without using one.
You’re okay, Phu?
Are you hurt anywhere?
Just when I had decided to send him back
this guy, the one I once thought
was crazy, is changing my world.
He’s making my heart beat
in a way it never has before.
What should I do?
English Subtitles by Saowalak K.
Knock, knock, knock.
Who’s there?
Nong Grade 10 calling
P' Grade 12, is anyone there?
If you hear me, please
send an alien signal back.
You should have answered him, Ai Cir.
I'll find a way to send
you back to your world
so you can be with
the Phukan you belong to.
I know how you feel about him.
But let me make it clear—you’ve
got nothing going on with him.
As far as I know,
you only talked to him once.
- And that time you—
- Ai Wim.
Aren’t you gonna kiss?